(Penny:)She would clearly like
to have a physical relationship with you.
(Penny:)So, what are you doing?
(Leonard:)All right, we're down the rabbit hole.
What are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Well, first of all, I'm quite fond of Amy.
(Penny:)Then what's the problem?
(Sheldon:)Penny...
(Sheldon:)...all my life I have been uncomfortable...
(Sheldon:)...with the sort of physical contact
that comes easily to others...
(Sheldon:)...handshaking, hugging...
(Sheldon:)...prostate exams.
(Sheldon:)But I'm working on it, you know?
(Sheldon:)Just recently, I had to put VapoRub
on Amy's chest.
(Sheldon:)A year ago,
that would have been unthinkable.
(Leonard:)Now you know how I feel
when I have to put it on you.
(Penny:)Okay, hang on.
(Penny:)Are you saying
someday you and Amy might...
(Penny:)...actually get physical?
(Sheldon:)It's a possibility.